<Document>
  # Cybernetic Beasts

  <Box>
	  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingCyberneticBeastMantle" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingCyberneticBeastMantleWorkEngineering" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingCyberneticBeastMantleWorkSalvage" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingCyberneticBeastMantleSecurity" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingCyberneticBeastMantleMedical" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingCyberneticBeastMantleBlueshieldOfficer" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingCyberneticBeastMantleCommand" Caption=""/>
  </Box>

  Cybernetic beasts are a subset of vulpkanin. They have been augmented with a removable visor, or "mantle".
  This mantle connects to the beast's head with a set of pogo-pins. In practice, this means that beasts can 
  wear each-other's mantles, but a mantle will provide no benefit to somebody who isn't a cybernetic beast.

  Cybernetic beasts are naturally short-sighted, but this is corrected by their mantle. Their mantle enhances
  their vision in more ways than one; It also gives the beast night vision and flash resistance.

  Cybernetic mantles are large. They cover the head and face of the wearer. Practically, this means that a beast
  must remove their mantle in order to use a gas mask, or a set of glasses.

  As well, due to the scarce nature of a beast's mantle, a mantle may sometimes become a target for thieves.
  
  ## Background

  During the early 2400s, Razzi Research and Technology, in their endless pursuit to allow colonists to live on 
  all sorts of worlds, created a set of cybernetic augments are are meant to "grow" with the user. Families 
  that had worked under them for generations were given the chance for their children to be "gifted" these augments
  for testing.

  Due to their simliarty with drawings and photos of old Atlam predators, augmented children would often be labeled 
  as "cybernetic beasts" by the wider population.

</Document>